<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Safecrop Insight</string>
    <string name="version">Version: 2025.05.25</string>

    <string name="search_by_farmer_code">Search by farmer code</string>
    <string name="no_farmer_available">No farmer available</string>
    <string name="no_training_available">No training available</string>
    <string name="load_farmer_list">Load Farmer List</string>
    <string name="farmer_list">Farmer List</string>
    <string name="load_train_topic">Load Training Topic</string>
    <string name="train_list">Training List</string>

    <string name="iis_photo">Photo of farm</string>
    <string name="loaded_farmers">0</string>

    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="select_choice">Select answer</string>
    <string name="select_farm_units">Select farm units</string>
    <string name="select_farm_visited">Select farm visited</string>
    <string name="select_com">Select community</string>
    <string name="select_district">Select district</string>
    <string name="select_gender">Select gender</string>
    <string name="_01_01_2024">01/01/2024</string>
    <string name="select_date">SELECT DATE</string>
    <string name="enter_name">Enter name</string>
    <string name="enter_number">Enter number</string>
    <string name="enter_m_number">Enter mobile number</string>
    <string name="enter_agent_name">Enter your full name</string>
    <string name="enter_farmer_name">Enter farmer name</string>
    <string name="get_location">Get Location</string>
    <string name="get_photo">Get Photo</string>
    <string name="get_idcard_photo">Photo of ID Card</string>
    <string name="get_farmer_photo">Photo of Farmer</string>
    <string name="get_tp_photo">Photo of Sign/Thumbprint</string>
    <string name="dash_for_geo_location">-.------- -.-------</string>

    <string name="enter_national_id"> Enter National ID</string>
    <string name="enter_farmerid"> Enter farm ID</string>
    <string name="enter_wages"> Enter wages</string>
    <string name="iis_pj"> Provide justification</string>

    <!--Internal Inspection Survey-->
    <string name="iis_q1">(1) Name of internal inspector</string>
    <string name="iis_q2">(2) Farmer name</string>
    <string name="iis_q3">(3) Gender</string>
    <string name="iis_q4">(4) National ID number</string>
    <string name="iis_q5">(5) Year of Birth</string>
    <string name="iis_q6">(6) Internal Group Member /Farm ID</string>
    <string name="iis_q7">(7) Farmer mobile number</string>
    <string name="iis_q8">(8) District</string>
    <string name="iis_q9">(9) Community</string>
    <string name="iis_q10">(10) Number of farm units</string>
    <string name="iis_q11">(11) The farm you visited (e.g. Farm 1, Farm 2, Farm 3)</string>
    <string name="iis_q12">(12) Total Farm area (ha)</string>
    <string name="iis_q13">(13) Total certified crop area (ha)</string>
    <string name="iis_q14">(14) Previous Year’s Harvest (Kg)</string>
    <string name="iis_q15">(15) Current Year Yield Estimate (Kg)</string>
    <string name="iis_q16">(16) Date of internal inspection</string>
    <string name="iis_q17">(17) Number of permanent workers</string>
    <string name="iis_q18">(17.1) Name of permanent worker1</string>
    <string name="iis_q19">(17.1) Gender of permanent worker1</string>
    <string name="iis_q20">(17.1) Year of birth of permanent worker1</string>
    <string name="iis_q21">(17.1) Wages of permanent worker1</string>
    <string name="iis_q22">(17.2) Name of permanent worker2</string>
    <string name="iis_q23">(17.2) Gender of permanent worker2</string>
    <string name="iis_q24">(17.2) Year of birth of permanent worker2</string>
    <string name="iis_q25">(17.2) Wages of permanent worker2</string>
    <string name="iis_q26">(17.3) Name of permanent worker3</string>
    <string name="iis_q27">(17.3) Gender of permanent worker3</string>
    <string name="iis_q28">(17.3) Year of birth of permanent worker3</string>
    <string name="iis_q29">(17.3) Wages of permanent worker3</string>
    <string name="iis_q30">(17.4) Name of permanent worker4</string>
    <string name="iis_q31">(17.4) Gender of permanent worker4</string>
    <string name="iis_q32">(17.4) Year of birth of permanent worker4</string>
    <string name="iis_q33">(17.4) Wages of permanent worker4</string>
    <string name="iis_q34">(17.5) Name of permanent worker5</string>
    <string name="iis_q35">(17.5) Gender of permanent worker5</string>
    <string name="iis_q36">(17.5) Year of birth of permanent worker5</string>
    <string name="iis_q37">(17.5) Wages of permanent worker5</string>
    <string name="iis_q38">(18) Number of temporary workers</string>
    <string name="iis_q39">(19) First year of RA certification</string>
    <string name="iis_q40">(20) Household size</string>
    <string name="iis_q41">(21) Year of Certification</string>
    <string name="iis_q42">(1.2.1) Management complies with applicable laws and collective bargaining agreements (CBA) within the scope of the Rainforest Alliance Sustainable Agriculture Standard. Producer is aware of the applicable laws that governs certification.</string>
    <string name="iis_q43">(1.2.6) An up-to-date list of permanent and temporary workers is kept, containing for each worker: (ie: Full name, Gender, Year of birth, Wages)</string>
    <string name="iis_q44">(1.2.8) Does the farmer understand the content of this agreement? Does farmer have a copy of the signed contract?</string>
    <string name="iis_q45">(FED1) Have you received training this year?</string>
    <string name="iis_q46">(1.2.9) Records for certification purposes and compliance are kept for at least four years.</string>
    <string name="iis_q47">(1.2.11) A sketch of the farm is available, including: the production area of certified crop, forests, water bodies and buildings.</string>
    <string name="iis_q48">(1.5.1) Inspector checks if the farmer is aware of the grievance mechanism that the group has in place</string>
    <string name="iis_q49">(2.1.8) Group members keep sales receipts, including name of group member, group member ID, date, product type and volume.</string>
    <string name="iis_q50">(3.2.1) Has the farmer received the RA sustainability differential for the cocoa delivered last year?</string>
    <string name="iis_q51">(4.1.1) Plant varieties for planting, grafting and renovation are selected based on quality, productivity, resistance to pests and diseases and on suitability for the climate during the lifetime of the plants. Planting materials are free of pests and diseases.</string>
    <string name="iis_q52">(4.1.2) New plantings have a well-established cropping system which takes into account (e.g. Requirements of the variety used, Geographical, ecological and agronomic conditions, Diversification and intercropping crops with different rooting depths and soil uses to enhance soil quality and health, Planting density)</string>
    <string name="iis_q53">(4.2.2) Producers carry out pruning according to the requirement in 4.2.1 Indicator: (ie: % of group members that adequately prune according to crop needs, agro ecological conditions and applicable pruning guidelines)</string>
    <string name="iis_q54">(4.2.2/2) Group member pruning adequately</string>
    <string name="iis_q55">(4.2.3) Producers renovate the certified crop when needed according to age, disease or other causes, to maintain productivity. This includes replanting production area, gap filling and grafting.</string>
    <string name="iis_q56">(4.3.1) The certified crop is not genetically modified (GMO).</string>
    <string name="iis_q57">(4.3.2) There are no genetically modified (GMO) crops on the farm.</string>
    <string name="iis_q58">(4.4.4) Producers use organic fertilizers and by-products available at farm level first, and supplement by inorganic fertilizer if nutrients are still lacking. To minimize risk, animal manure is hot composted before use as a fertilizer. Producers store animal manure and compost at least 25 meters away from any water body.</string>
    <string name="iis_q59">(4.4.7) Producers monitor and optimize the use of organic and inorganic fertilizers.</string>
    <string name="iis_q60">(4.5.2) Producers regularly monitor pests and their principal natural enemies.</string>
    <string name="iis_q61">(4.5.3) When threshold levels of pests are reached, producers firstly try biological, physical, and other non-chemical control methods, and document this. When such methods are proven not to be effective, producers can do agrochemical applications, as advised by a competent technician and/or upon the advice or instruction by an official national organization.</string>
    <string name="iis_q62">(4.5.4) Producers and workers that are involved in pest management activities are trained about the IPM strategy.</string>
    <string name="iis_q63">(4.5.7) Producers monitor and reduce the use of pesticides. (Name of pesticide, Quantity used, Target pest)</string>
    <string name="iis_q64">(4.6.1) No agrochemicals are used that are: (• On the Rainforest Alliance Prohibited List, • Prohibited by applicable law, • Not legally registered in the country where the farm is located, Producers use only agrochemicals sold by authorized vendors, in original and sealed packaging.</string>
    <string name="iis_q65">(4.6.2) If producers use pesticides included on the Risk Mitigation list, all respective risk mitigation practices, as described in Annex 7, Pesticides Management, are implemented.</string>
    <string name="iis_q66">(4.6.3) Persons handling pesticides are skilled in the preparation and application of pesticides, and receive annual training. Persons handling pesticides use the Personal Protective Equipment (PPE) as prescribed in the product’s label or Material Safety Data Sheet (MSDS). If there is no information, basic protective clothing with additional items is worn according to the potential risk and as recommended by a competent technician.</string>
    <string name="iis_q67">(4.6.4) Persons handling pesticides bath, change and wash clothes after application.</string>
    <string name="iis_q68">(4.6.5) Pesticides are prepared and applied according to the label, MSDS or security tag, or as recommended by an official national organization or a competent technician, especially with regards to: • Safe transport to area of application • Respecting the correct dosage • Using appropriate equipment and techniques • appropriate weather conditions • Respecting restricted entry intervals (REI), including warning signs in local language.</string>
    <string name="iis_q69">(4.6.6) Mechanisms are established and maintained to avoid contamination by pesticides, through spray drift or other pathways, from treated areas to other areas including all aquatic and terrestrial natural ecosystems and infrastructure. Such mechanisms include non-crop vegetative barriers, non-application zones or other effective mechanisms.</string>
    <string name="iis_q70">(4.6.7) Aerial application is only allowed under the conditions as outlined in Annex 7: Pesticides Management.</string>
    <string name="iis_q71">(4.6.8) Pesticide applications are recorded. Records include: • Product brand name and active ingredient(s) • Date and time of application • Location and area (size) of application • Dosage and volume • Crop • Name(s) of applicator(s) • Target pest</string>
    <string name="iis_q72">(4.6.9) Empty pesticides containers and application equipment are washed three times, and rinsing water is used in the last batch of the mix to apply to the crop. After application of pesticides, application equipment is washed three times, and the surplus mix is disposed of in way that minimizes the negative impact on the environment and human health.</string>
    <string name="iis_q73">(4.6.10) Agrochemicals and application equipment are stored in accordance with the label instructions and in a way that minimizes negative impact on the environment and human health. Agrochemicals are stored in their original containers or packaging. Facilities for storing agrochemicals and application equipment are: • Dry, clean, well-ventilated • Made from non-absorbent material • Safely locked and accessible only by trained handlers • Not accessible to children • Separated from crop, food products, and packaging materials</string>
    <string name="iis_q74">(4.7.1) Producers conserve and optimize quality and quantity of product during harvest and post-harvest handling, including: loading, processing, packing, transportation, and storage. This includes: • Products are harvested at the right time and interval to optimize quality • Harvesting damages to the plant are minimized for future production • Contamination by foreign matter, cleaning products and agrochemicals, microbes and pests are prevented • Damage due to humidity is prevented • Products are stored in a cool, dry, well-ventilated and dark place • Maintenance and cleaning of harvest and postharvest tools, machinery and equipment • Packaging materials are used that are suitable and approved for food products</string>
    <string name="iis_q75">(5.1.8) The management assures good functioning of the assess-and-address system. For this purpose, from year one onwards, a yearly assessment of the assess-and-address system for the relevant issue(s) is conducted, based on the following five elements: • Effective implementation of mitigation measures • Effective training on relevant assess-and-address topics • Effective cooperation with external actors • Effective monitoring of the assess-and-address system • Effective internal collaboration on assess-and-address topics</string>
    <string name="iis_q76">(5.2.1) Workers have the right to form and join a union or workers’ organization of their own choice and to take part in collective bargaining, without prior authorization from the employer, and in accordance with national law. Workers’ representatives are elected democratically among workers in regular, free elections.</string>
    <string name="iis_q77">(5.2.2) Workers are not subject to discrimination or retaliation for reasons of past or present workers’ organization or union membership or activities. Management does not punish, bribe or otherwise influence union members or workers’ representatives. Records are kept of terminations of employment, including the reason for termination and workers affiliation with a union or workers’ organization.</string>
    <string name="iis_q78">(5.2.3) Management provides workers’ representatives reasonable paid time off from work to carry out their representation functions and attend meetings. Where needed, management provides the worker representatives with reasonable facilities including meeting space, means of communication and child care. Management keeps records of the minutes from meetings with worker organizations and / or trade unions.</string>
    <string name="iis_q79">(5.3.1) Permanent and temporary workers who are employed for more than three consecutive months have a written employment contract signed by both parties. The worker receives a copy of the contract at the time of signing. Permanent and temporary workers employed for fewer than three months must have at least verbal contracts in place.</string>
    <string name="iis_q80">(5.3.2) Management does not engage in arrangements or practices designed to eliminate or reduce workers’ pay and/or benefits such as employing temporary workers for permanent or ongoing tasks.</string>
    <string name="iis_q81">(5.3.4) Workers receive at least the applicable minimum wage or the wage negotiated in a Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA), whichever is higher. For production, quota or piece work, the payment must be at least the minimum wage based on a 48-hour working week or national legal working hours limit, whichever is lower.</string>
    <string name="iis_q82">(5.3.5) Deductions from wages are permitted only if provided by national law or CBA. Voluntary wage deductions such as advance payments, union membership, or loans can only be made with written or verbal consent from the worker. Wage deductions as a disciplinary measure are not allowed. Deductions for work related to tools, equipment or gear are not allowed unless those are permitted by law. In-kind benefits must be in accordance with national law; however, they cannot exceed 30% of the total remuneration.</string>
    <string name="iis_q83">(5.3.7) Workers are paid regularly at scheduled intervals agreed both by the worker and the employer, but must be at least monthly. Group members maintain records, per worker, of hours worked (regular and overtime) and/or volume produced, calculation of wages, in-kind benefits and deductions. The record is signed by each worker when he/she receives payment. </string>
    <string name="iis_q84">(5.3.8) Work of equal value is remunerated with equal pay without discrimination e.g. on gender or type of worker, ethnicity, age, color, religion, political opinion, nationality, social origin or others.</string>
    <string name="iis_q85">(5.3.10) If labor providers are used, name, contact and, if labor provider is officially registered, official registration number of the labor provider is recorded. All recruitment fees are paid by the farm, not by workers.</string>
    <string name="iis_q86">(5.4.4) Total remuneration of workers (wages, monetary benefits, in-kind benefits) is increasing towards and beyond the applicable Living Wage benchmark following the targets in the wage improvement plan.</string>
    <string name="iis_q87">(5.5.1) Workers do not work more than eight regular working hours per day and 48 regular working hours per week. In addition, workers have at least a 30-minute break after a maximum of six consecutive hours of work and are granted at least one full day of rest after a maximum of six consecutive days of work. The regular work hours of guards do not exceed 56 hours per week on average per year.</string>
    <string name="iis_q88">(5.5.2) Overtime work is voluntary and only permitted if it meets requirements in criterion 5.5.2 of the standard.</string>
    <string name="iis_q89">(5.5.3) Pregnant permanent workers are entitled to paid maternity leave of at least 14 weeks, of which maximum six weeks before the expected due date and at least six weeks after giving birth, and receive maternity rights and benefits. Breastfeeding women have two additional 30-minute breaks per day and a space for breastfeeding to nurture the child. </string>
    <string name="iis_q90">(5.5.4) Workers’ children younger than the applicable minimum working age coming with their parents to the workplace: • Are provided with a safe place to stay according to their age • Are under the supervision of adults at all times</string>
    <string name="iis_q91">(5.6.2) First aid boxes are available to workers for the treatment of work-related injuries. The boxes are placed at the central locations of production, processing, and maintenance sites. Trained first aid employees are present during working hours. </string>
    <string name="iis_q92">(5.6.3) Group members and workers know where to go in case of an emergency.</string>
    <string name="iis_q93">(5.6.6) Workers always have access to safe and sufficient drinking water.</string>
    <string name="iis_q94">(5.6.9) Persons that work in hazardous situations (e.g. under challenging terrains, with machines or with hazardous materials) use appropriate Personal Protective Equipment (PPE). These persons are trained in the use of the PPE and have access to the PPE free of charge.</string>
    <string name="iis_q95">(5.6.10) All tools used by the workers are in good working condition. Machines have clear instructions on safe usage that can be understood by the workers, and dangerous parts are guarded or encased. Workers using such machines are appropriately trained. Operating machinery have the applicable licenses. Machinery and other equipment are stored safely when not in use.</string>
    <string name="iis_q96">(5.6.11) Female workers who are pregnant, nursing, or have recently given birth are not assigned to activities that pose a risk to the woman’s, unborn children, or infant’s health. In cases of job reassignment, there is no reduction in remuneration. No pregnancy tests are requested.</string>
    <string name="iis_q97">(5.6.12) Workers may leave situations with imminent danger without seeking employer’s permission and without being penalized.</string>
    <string name="iis_q98">(5.7.3) Workers and their families that are housed or lodged on-site have safe, clean and decent living quarters considering local conditions and the possibilities of each producer. • Access to safe drinking water. • Adequate sanitary and washing facilities. Safety and privacy of vulnerable groups is ensured, at least by well-lit and lockable facilities.</string>
    <string name="iis_q99">(5.8.2) The producer has legal and legitimate right to use the land. In case of dispute involving indigenous people and local communities, large farms and individually certified farms follow an FPIC process in accordance with the Rainforest Alliance FPIC Annex to attain the required conflict resolution and remediation.</string>
    <string name="iis_q100">(6.1.1) From January 1st 2014 onward, natural forests and other natural ecosystems have not been converted into agricultural production or other land uses.</string>
    <string name="iis_q101">(6.1.2) Production or processing does not occur in protected areas or their officially designated buffer zones, except where it complies with applicable law.</string>
    <string name="iis_q102">(6.2.2) Farms maintain all remnant forest trees, except when these pose hazards to people or infrastructure. Other native trees on the farm and their harvesting are sustainably managed in a way that the same quantity and quality of trees is maintained on the farm.</string>
    <string name="iis_q103">(6.2.3) Producers maintain and management monitors natural vegetation cover and reports annually on the indicator from year one onwards. If there is less than 10% of the total area under natural vegetation cover or less than 15% for farms growingshade-tolerant crops, management sets targets and takes actions for farms to reach these thresholds as required in 6.2.4. Natural vegetation is vegetation made up predominantly of native or locally adapted species, resembling in species composition and structure the vegetation that occurs or would occur in the absence of human interference. Natural vegetation can include one or more of the following (not exclusive): • Riparian buffers • Conservation areas within the farm • Natural vegetation in agroforestry systems • Border plantings, live fences and barriers around housing and infrastructure, or in other ways • Conservation and restoration areas outside the certified farm that effectively provide long-term protection of the subject areas (for at least 25 years) and yield additional conservation value and protection status relative to the status quo Indicator: • % of total farm area under natural vegetation cover</string>
    <string name="iis_q104">(6.2.3.1) Number of remnant trees on the farms Percentage estimate of the farmers total area with natural vegetation</string>
    <string name="iis_q105">(6.3.1) Farms maintain existing riparian buffers adjacent to aquatic ecosystems.</string>
    <string name="iis_q106">(6.3.2) Producers maintain the following additional safeguards for the protection of drinking water in case the farm is located closer than 50 m to a source of drinking water.</string>
    <string name="iis_q107">(6.4.1) Threatened animals and plants are not hunted, killed, fished, collected or trafficked. Additionally, producers and workers do not hunt other animals, with the following exceptions: • Producers of small farms may hunt non-threatened animals for non-commercial use only • Producers may hunt vertebrate wildlife pests on the farm only following the farm’s integrated pest management (IPM) plan, and only as a measure of last resort. Explosives or toxic substances are never used for hunting, fishing, or control of wildlife pests.</string>
    <string name="iis_q108">(6.4.2) Producers do not hold wildlife in captivity. Captive wild animals that were present on the farm before the earliest certification date are sent to professional shelters or may be held only for non-commercial purposes for the remainder of their lives. </string>
    <string name="iis_q109">(6.4.3) Producers do not intentionally introduce or release invasive species. Producers do not dispose of existing invasive species or their parts in aquatic ecosystems.</string>
    <string name="iis_q110">(6.4.4) Producers do not use wildlife for processing or harvesting of any crop (e.g. luwak for coffee, monkeys for coconut, etc.).</string>
    <string name="iis_q111">(6.4.5) Erosion by water and wind is reduced through practices such as re-vegetation of steep areas and terracing.</string>
    <string name="iis_q112">(6.4.6) Fire is not used for preparing or cleaning fields, except when specifically justified in the IPM plan.</string>
    <string name="iis_q113">(6.5.1) Producers comply with the applicable law for the withdrawal of surface or groundwater for agricultural, domestic or processing purposes.</string>
    <string name="iis_q114">(6.5.2) If required, producers have a license or permit (or a pending request) for the withdrawal of surface or groundwater for agricultural, domestic, or processing purposes.</string>
    <string name="iis_q115">(6.6.2) Human sewage, sludge, and sewage water is not used for production and/or processing activities.</string>
    <string name="iis_q116">(6.6.3) Wastewater from processing operations is not applied to land unless it has undergone treatment to remove particulates and toxins. If treated wastewater is used for irrigation, in addition to the wastewater parameters, it must comply with the wastewater parameters for irrigation.</string>
    <string name="iis_q117">(6.7.1) Waste is stored, treated and disposed of in ways that do not pose health or safety risks to people, animals or natural ecosystems. Waste is stored and disposed of only in designated areas and not disposed of in natural or aquatic ecosystems. Non-organic waste is not left on the land.</string>
    <string name="iis_q118">(6.7.2) Producers do not burn waste, except in incinerators technically designed for the specific type of waste.</string>
    <string name="iis_q119">(22)Get Geo-Location</string>

    <string name="enter_size">Enter size</string>
    <string name="enter_year">Enter year</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="fname">fName</string>
    <string name="lname">lName</string>

    <string name="name">Name</string>

    <string name="aa_aa_aa001">AA-AA-AA001</string>
    <string name="farmer_fname">fName</string>
    <string name="farmer_lname">lName</string>
    <string name="farmer_district">District</string>
    <string name="search_farmer">Search Farmer</string>
    <string name="farmer_not_found">farmer not found</string>
    <string name="dash">-</string>
    <string name="farmer_list_title">Farmer List</string>
    <string name="farmer_profiling">Farmer Profiling</string>
    <string name="inspection_part3">Inspection (Part 2)</string>
    <string name="report_bug">Report Bug</string>

    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_password">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="sustainability_certification_surveys">Sustainability/Certification Surveys</string>
    <string name="sustainability_certification_menu">Sustainability/Certification Menu</string>
    <string name="profiling_inspection_training">Profiling, Inspection, Training</string>
    <string name="clmrs_menu">CLMRS Menu</string>
    <string name="community_development_surveys">Com. Dev. Surveys</string>
    <string name="community_school_household_child">Community, School, Household, Child</string>
    <string name="org_pro">Organic Projects</string>
    <string name="org_pro_report">Organic project report</string>
    <string name="train">Training and Sensitisation Tracker</string>
    <string name="start_a_new_community_survey">Start a new community survey</string>
    <string name="child_survey">Child Survey</string>
    <string name="start_a_new_household_survey">Start a new household survey</string>
    <string name="start_a_new_school_survey">Start a new school survey</string>
    <string name="household_survey">Household Survey</string>
    <string name="school_survey">School Survey</string>
    <string name="start_a_new_child_survey">Start a new child survey</string>
    <string name="inspection_survey">Inspection Survey</string>
    <string name="profile_new_farmer">Profile new farmer</string>
    <string name="farmer_training">Farmer Training</string>
    <string name="start_a_new_training">Start a new training</string>
    <string name="start_a_new_inspection_survey">Start a new inspection survey</string>
    <string name="backup_com_survey">Community Survey</string>
    <string name="backup_sch_survey">School Survey</string>
    <string name="backup_hh_survey">Household Survey</string>
    <string name="backup_ob_survey">Observation Survey</string>
    <string name="backup_ch_survey">Child Survey</string>
    <string name="backup">Backup</string>
    <string name="cloud_backup">Cloud Backup</string>
    <string name="cloud_backup_header">CLOUD BACKUP</string>
    <string name="cloud_backup_sub_header">Cloud Backup Options</string>
    <string name="local_backup">Local Backup</string>
    <string name="local_backup_header">LOCAL BACKUP</string>
    <string name="local_backup_sub_header">Local Backup Options</string>


    //Community
    <string name="com_survey">Community Survey</string>


    //School
    <string name="sch_survey">School Survey</string>
    <string name="producer_entry">Producer Entry</string>


    //Children
    <string name="ch_view">Child Details</string>
    <string name="ch_edit">Update Child Details</string>
    <string name="ch_survey">Child Survey</string>


    <string name="update_gmrsurvey">Update Profiled Farmer</string>
    <string name="user_name">User Name</string>
    <string name="sustainability_certification_survey">Sustainability/Certification Survey</string>


    <string name="district">District</string>
    <string name="community_survey">Community Survey</string>

    <string name="surveyed_children">Surveyed Children</string>

    <string name="surveyed_communities">Surveyed Communities</string>

    <string name="surveyed_household">Surveyed Household</string>

    <string name="surveyed_schools">Surveyed Schools</string>
    <string name="farmers_entered">Farmers Entered</string>

    <string name="farmer_details">Farmer Details</string>
    <string name="surveyed_school">Surveyed Schools</string>
    <string name="surveyed_com">Surveyed Communities</string>

    <string name="greeting">Hi, %s</string>
    <string name="environmental_projects">Environmental Projects</string>
    <string name="environment_project_report">Environment project report</string>
    <string name="exiting_application">EXITING APPLICATION</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_you_want_to_exit">You are exiting the app\nAre you sure you want to exit?</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="app_settings">APP SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="survey_details">SURVEY DETAILS</string>
    <string name="account_details">ACCOUNT DETAILS</string>
    <string name="check_circle_outline_green">check_circle_outline_green</string>
    <string name="name_domain_com">name@domain.com</string>
    <string name="_0000000000">0000000000</string>
    <string name="user_dtails">User Dtails</string>
    <string name="forward_arrow_outline">Forward Arrow Outline</string>
    <string name="info_icon_outline">Info Icon Outline</string>
    <string name="observation_survey">Observation Survey</string>
    <string name="community">Community</string>

    <string name="observed_farmers">Observed Farmers</string>
    <string name="profiled_farmers">Profiled Farmers</string>
    <string name="date_time">DateTime</string>
    <string name="selected_or_captured_image">Selected or Captured Image</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="no_record_found">No Record Found</string>

    <string name="training_attendance">Training Attendance</string>
    <string name="added_face">Added Face</string>
    <string name="add_face">Add Face</string>
    <string name="recognise_face">Recognise Face</string>
    <string name="sync_info">Sync Survey</string>
    <string name="start_date">Start Date</string>
    <string name="end_date">End Date</string>
    <string name="filter">Filter</string>
    <string name="total_records_synced_0">Total Records Synced: 0</string>
    <string name="filter_by">Filter By:</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="capture_or_select_image">Capture or Select Image</string>
    <string name="openstreetmap_contributors_data_available_under_the_open_database_license_odbl">© OpenStreetMap contributors. Data available under the Open Database License (ODbL).</string>
    <string name="_0_000_0_000">0.000, 0.000</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="training_description">Training description</string>
    <string name="training_topic">Training topic</string>
    <string name="training_topics">Training Topics</string>
    <string name="hrdd_norad">HRDD - NORAD</string>
    <string name="dashboard_menu">Dashboard Menu</string>
    <string name="community_risk_assessment">Community risk assessment</string>
    <string name="community_assessment">Community Assessment</string>
    <string name="child_forced_labour_assessment">Child / forced labour assessment</string>
    <string name="start_new_assessment">Start new assessment</string>
    <string name="gender_risk_assessment">Gender risk assessment</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->

    <string name="save_attendance">Save Attendance</string>
    <string name="training_tracker">Training Tracker</string>
    <string name="community_assessment_infobs">Community Assessment</string>
    <string name="child_forced_labour_assmt">Child/Forced Labour Assmt.</string>
    <string name="gender_assessment">Gender Assessment</string>
    <string name="producer_entry_">Producer Entry</string>
    <string name="start_new_entry">Start new entry</string>

</resources>